# **Natan Oihman**

# Fullstack Developer

## **Experience**

## Omnitelecom - Fullstack engineer

2023-2024, Ramat Gan

Omnitelecom is a start-up which provides cloud telephony services for enterprises including Asuta, Maccabi and more. We were a small team that took operations and responsibilities ranging over lots of technologies from infrastructure to devOps and client facing apps.

- Researched, designed and implemented inhouse tools for customer success teams, this resulted in customer retention and saving lots of time for our support team.
- Worked with our marketing team to design and develop client dedicated apps.
- Embedding text to speech and speech to text during phone calls according to customers' needs and our product team's design.
- Took part in the ongoing development process, maintaining automatic phone reminders code and company infrastructure code including environment in the cloud.

# IDF Air Force - Integration technician and QA

2013-2016

- Acquired technical knowledge in the fields of IT, networking, QA and cyber.
- Managing unix \ Linux and windows servers.
- Planning network layouts using Cisco technology.
- Planning and building testing environments while monitoring data and solving network and hardware issues.

# **Education**

# **Ben-Gurion University of the Negev** BSC Physics and philosophy

2018-2022

- Python
- High level of math and analytical skills

# Braude Academic College of Engineering Practical electric engineer with computer science specialization

2011-2013

- Designing and building electric circuits
- C programming
- Building a project (digital delay for electric guitar) using Arduino hardware
- VHDL programming

### +972543080851

natanoih@gmail.com Linkedin Github Personal Site

### **About me**

Bsc in Physics and Philosophy

Self taught Fullstack developer with proven experience, keeping myself updated on the recent new features in everything I am working with.

In addition, I am a professional bass guitar player. Being a musician over the years has taught me a great deal about cooperating with others and working as a team.

### **Tech stack**

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, TypeScript.
- Frontend React (Typescript, Tailwind, UI libraries, custom hooks, UI/UX), HTMX.
- State management Redux, Jotai, React Context api.
- Backend NextJs, Node.Js, Golang, Django (python) and Perl.
- Routing, Server Side rendering, Server actions, API, Server side fetching and db integrations.
- Docker, Cloud, Git.
- Rest API.
- SQL(postgres), Redis, MongoDB.
- Scripting and managing linux servers with cron jobs, perl/python/Go scripting and Bash

•